<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Javascript on Austin Wang</title>
    <link>https://dafondo.github.io/tools/javascript/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Javascript on Austin Wang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>austin.wang0311@gmail.com (Austin Wang)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>austin.wang0311@gmail.com (Austin Wang)</webMaster>
    <copyright>(c) 2017 Austin Wang.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://dafondo.github.io/tools/javascript/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Dafondo.github.io</title>
      <link>https://dafondo.github.io/project/dafondo.github.io/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2017 22:07:31 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>austin.wang0311@gmail.com (Austin Wang)</author>
      <guid>https://dafondo.github.io/project/dafondo.github.io/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Link: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Dafondo/dafondo.github.io&#34;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;wazzit&#34;&gt;Wazzit?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;re here right now! This website allows me to easily share my projects with
the world. It&amp;rsquo;s built on &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt;, an amazing static website
engine, with the &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/enten/hyde-y&#34;&gt;Hyde-Y&lt;/a&gt; theme.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Originally I planned to use Jekyll, a different static site generator, but I
began noticing some performance issues, so I switched to Hugo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-i-gained&#34;&gt;What I Gained&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I definitely gained some insight into how static site generators handle and
organize data. Hugo makes it really easy to get a site up and running while
still being flexible enough to mold to my personal needs. The only entry barrier
 is learning the organization schemes each generator likes to use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently I&amp;rsquo;ve received requests from friends to help them create personal
websites. One of the main problems is finding a platform that&amp;rsquo;s easily
maintainable by less technically-inclined people. For this reason, I&amp;rsquo;m not sure
I&amp;rsquo;d recommend Jekyll or Hugo to my friends. I still think platforms like
WordPress and Squarespace are better suited for this job.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MemeTrades (Old)</title>
      <link>https://dafondo.github.io/project/memetrades.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 04:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>austin.wang0311@gmail.com (Austin Wang)</author>
      <guid>https://dafondo.github.io/project/memetrades.com/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Links: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/QuadmasterXLII/memeClient&#34;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://hgreer.com/meme-dev/&#34;&gt;Old Version (Defunct)&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://memetrades.com/&#34;&gt;New MemeTrades.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Teammates: &lt;a href=&#34;http://hgreer.com/flask/&#34;&gt;Hastings Greer&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://subdavis.com/&#34;&gt;Brandon Davis&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://kylefeng28.github.io/&#34;&gt;Kyle Feng&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dafondo.github.io/images/memetrades.png&#34; alt=&#34;Memetrades.com&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;wazzit&#34;&gt;Wazzit?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was a website where users would start with 1000 &amp;ldquo;meme bucks&amp;rdquo; with which they could buy and sell shares in memes. Users could make new memes and add them to the market at any time simply by typing them in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;my-role&#34;&gt;My Role&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I worked on small parts of the frontend and UX, such as user the portfolio display and buy/sell interface. I also worked on a D3 bubble graph visualizer for the market. This was my introduction to D3 and I still have a lot to learn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-future-of-meme-trading&#34;&gt;The Future of Meme Trading&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;Brandon Davis&#34;&gt;Brandon&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;Hastings Greer&#34;&gt;Hastings&lt;/a&gt; have continued developing MemeTrades.com with entirely new backend and frontend. They&amp;rsquo;ve reached 1000 users at the time of this piece. Go check it out at &lt;a href=&#34;http://memetrades.com/&#34;&gt;MemeTrades.com&lt;/a&gt;! I have not contributed to this new MemeTrades website.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Farewell Simulator</title>
      <link>https://dafondo.github.io/project/farewellsimulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2017 15:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>austin.wang0311@gmail.com (Austin Wang)</author>
      <guid>https://dafondo.github.io/project/farewellsimulator/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Links: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/QuadmasterXLII/farewell-simulator&#34;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://globalgamejam.org/2017/games/farewell-simulator&#34;&gt;GGJ Team Page&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://quadmasterxlii.github.io/farewell-simulator/&#34;&gt;Play Now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Teammates: &lt;a href=&#34;https://subdavis.com/&#34;&gt;Brandon Davis&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://hgreer.com/flask/&#34;&gt;Hastings Greer&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://forrestli.com/&#34;&gt;Forrest Li&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://dafondo.github.io/images/farewell-sim.png&#34; width=&#34;400&#34; height=&#34;400&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;wazzit&#34;&gt;Wazzit?&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My team and I made this game at Global Game Jam 2017. The theme of the game jam was &amp;ldquo;waves&amp;rdquo;, which my group interpreted as the hand motion used to say goodbye.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-plot&#34;&gt;The Plot!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this game, you (a mighty general) are waving guests out of your house after a wonderful and exciting soirée. Unfortunately, you live beside a busy multi-lane highway and all of your guests decided to park across the street. The party left them a little tipsy so they&amp;rsquo;re at high risk for vehicular collision. The good news is that your guests have great respect for you as a friend and a general. When you wave at them, they stop in their tracks and wave back. Using your military experience and tactical prowess, you must guide them across the highway by waving at them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;features&#34;&gt;Features&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only control in this game is wiggling your cursor across the screen to wave at guests. There&amp;rsquo;s also a camera mode that is meant to work with hand detection, but it requires high contrast between hand and background, so it doesn&amp;rsquo;t work very well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The default game mode is campaign which features a few preset levels designed by hand; these levels are all solvable. Survival mode is an endless high score mode that features randomly generated levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;my-role&#34;&gt;My Role&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was responsible for creating most of the artwork (to see all of the sprites please play survival mode). I wrote only a small amount of the code/style, and the little that I did write was eventually refactored and rewritten.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>